{
    "subject": "resource/Michael_Dell",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Houston",
    "human_readable": "Michael Dell was born in Houston.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8879315257072449,
            "question": "Where was Michael Dell born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7685146331787109,
            "question": "When was Michael Dell born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42164894938468933,
            "question": "What is Michael Dell known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29281193017959595,
            "question": "Did Michael Dell found a company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22403104603290558,
            "question": "What type of company did Michael Dell found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2033938467502594,
            "question": "What year was the company founded by Michael Dell established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18937966227531433,
            "question": "What is the name of the company Michael Dell founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1728680580854416,
            "question": "Is Michael Dell still involved with his company today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11807745695114136,
            "question": "What is the name of Michael Dell's company headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07897689193487167,
            "question": "Is Houston considered a major city in the United States?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Dell was born in Houston.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3926_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Michael Dell's company headquarters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3926_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Michael Dell still involved with his company today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3926_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the company Michael Dell founded?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3926_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3926_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3926_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3926_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3926_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3926_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3926_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3926_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3926_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3926_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3926_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided confirm that Michael Dell was indeed born in Houston, as mentioned in multiple files (40.txt, 4.txt, 96.txt, and others)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple instances confirming that Michael Dell was indeed born in Houston, Texas."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}